let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Algiers is the capital of?",
        answer: "Algeria",
        options: [ "Zambia", "Uruguay", "Algeria", "Tanzania" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Luanda is the capital of?",
        answer: "Angola",
        options: ["Sudan", "Angola","Venezuela","Swaziland" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Porto Novo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Benin",
        options: ["Tunisia","Gerogia","Senegal", "Benin" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Gaborone is the capital of?",
        answer: "Botswana",
        options: ["Botswana", "Sierra Leone","Guyana","Seychelles"]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Ouagadougou is the capital of?",
        answer: "Burkina Faso",
        options: ["Dijibouti","Mauritania","Gernada","Burkina Faso" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Gitega is the capital of?",
        answer: "Burundi",
        options: ["Mozambique", "Ecuador","Burundi","Rwanda"]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Youndé is the capital of?",
        answer: "Cameroon",
        options: ["south sudan","Cameroon", "Pakistan", "Somalia"]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Praia is the capital of?",
        answer: "Cape Verde",
        options: ["Cape Verde","Namibia","Syria","Sierra Leone"  ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Bangui is the capital of?",
        answer: "Central African Republic ",
        options: [
            "Solomon Islands",
            "Cuba",
            "Ghana",
            "Central African Republic "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " N’Djamena is the capital of?",
        answer: "Chad",
        options: [
            "Chad",
            "Tonga",
            "Libya",
            "Lima"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Moroni is the capital of?",
        answer: "Comros",
        options: [
            "Ethiopia",
            "Comoros",
            "Malawi",
            "Tuvalu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Brazzavile is the capital of?",
        answer: "Republic of the Congo",
        options: [
            "Laos",
            "Ghana",
            "Republic of the Congo",
            "Palau"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Kinshasa is the capital of?",
        answer: "Democratic Republic of the Congo ",
        options: [
            "Lesotho",
            "Democratic Republic of the Congo ",
            "The Gambia",
            "Mauritius"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Yamoussoukro is the capital of?",
        answer: "Côte d’IvoirePalau",
        options: [
            "Côte d’Ivoire",
            "Liberia",
            "Zaire",
            "Yemen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Djibouti City is the capital of?",
        answer: "Djibouti",
        options: [
            "Lesotho",
            "Armenia",
            "Guinea",
            "Djibouti"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Cairo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Egypt",
        options: [
            "Mauritius",
            "Egypt",
            "Maldives",
            "Namibia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Malabo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Equatorial Guinea",
        options: [
            "Jordon",
            "Cape Verde",
            "Comoros",
            "Equtorial Ginea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Asmara is the capital of?",
        answer: "Eritrea",
        options: [
            "Eritera",
            "Morocoo",
            "Tunisia",
            "Yemen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Addis Ababa is the capital of?",
        answer: "Ethiopia",
        options: [
            "Mauritania",
            "Ethiopia",
            "Madagascar",
            "Lebanon"
        ]
    },
    {
        
        numb: 20,
        question: "Libreville is the capital of?",
        answer: "Gabon",
        options: [
            "Côte d’Ivoire",
            "Liberia",
            "Gabon",
            "Libia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Banjul is the capital of?",
        answer: "The Gambia",
        options: [
            "Suriname",
            "Eritrea",
            "Zaire",
            "The Gambia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Accra is the capital of?",
        answer: "Ghana",
        options: [
            "Ghana",
            "Jordon",
            "Burundi",
            "Lesotho"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Canakry is the capital of?",
        answer: "Guinea",
        options: [
            "Chile",
            "Equatorial Guinea",
            "Misr",
            "Guinea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Bissau is the capital of?",
        answer: "Guinea-Bissau",
        options: [
            "chile",
            "Eritera",
            "Guinea-Bissau",
            "Libreville"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Nairobi is the capital of?",
        answer: "kenya",
        options: [
            "Jamaica",
            "Kenya",
            "Egypt",
            "Comoros"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "Maseru is the capital of?",
        answer: "Lesotho",
        options: [
            "Lesotho",
            "Sudan",
            "Japan",
            "Burundi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "Monrovia is the capital of?",
        answer: "Liberia",
        options: [
            "Botswana",
            "Armenia",
            "Misr",
            "Liberia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "Tripoli is the capital of?",
        answer: "Libya",
        options: [
            "Chad",
            "Libya",
            "Netherlands",
            "The Gambia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "Antananriva is the capital of?",
        answer: "Madagascar",
        options: [
            "Dijibouti",
            "Madagascar",
            "Morocco",
            "Cambodia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "Lilongwe is the capital of?",
        answer: "Malawi",
        options: [
            "Ginea-Bissau",
            "Burkina Faso",
            "South Africa",
            "Malawi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question: "Bamako is the capital of?",
        answer: "Mali",
        options: [ "Kenya", "Senegal", "Mali", "Libreville" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question: "Nouakchott is the capital of?",
        answer: "Mauritania",
        options: ["Mauritania", "Angola","Cambodia","Mauritius" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question: "Port Louis is the capital of?",
        answer: "Mauritius",
        options: ["Abyssinia","Mauritius","Russia", "Benin" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question: "Rabat is the capital of?",
        answer: "Morocco",
        options: ["Equatorial Guinea", "Morocco","Guatemala","South Sudan"]
    },
    {
        numb: 35,
        question: "Maputo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Mozambique",
        options: ["Algeria","Comoros","Mozambique","Burkina Faso" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 36,
        question: "Windhoek is the capital of?",
        answer: "Namibia",
        options: ["Angola", "Benin","Namibia","Ghana"]
    },
    {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Niamey is the capital of?",
        answer: "Niger",
        options: ["Mozambique","Finland", "Mauritania", "Niger"]
    },
    {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Abuja is the capital of?",
        answer: "Nigeria",
        options: ["Nigeria","Niger","Mexico","Guinea"  ]
    },
    {
        numb: 39,
        question: "Kigali is the capital of?",
        answer: "Rwanda ",
        options: [
            "Eritera",
            "Botswana",
            "Rwanda",
            "Central African Republic "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 40,
        question: "São Tomé is the capital of?",
        answer: "São Tomé and Príncipe",
        options: [
            "São Tomé and Príncipe",
            "Tonga",
            "Benin",
            "Lima"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 41,
        question: "Dakar is the capital of?",
        answer: "Senegal",
        options: [
            "Niger",
            "Comoros",
            "Senegal",
            "Tuvalu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 42,
        question: "Victoria is the capital of?",
        answer: "Seychelles",
        options: [
            "Seychelles",
            "Ghana",
            "Burundi",
            "Palau"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Freetown is the capital of?",
        answer: "Sierra Leone",
        options: [
            "Zimbabwe",
            "Sierra Leone",
            "Lebanon",
            "Mali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 44,
        question: "Mogadishu is the capital of?",
        answer: "Somalia",
        options: [
            "Equatorial Guinea",
            "Madagascar",
            "Paraguay",
            "Somalia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 45,
        question: "Pretoria is the capital of?",
        answer: "South Africa",
        options: [
            "South Africa",
            "Mozambique",
            "Eritrea",
            "Guyana"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 46,
        question: "Juba is the capital of?",
        answer: "South Sudan",
        options: [
            "Sudan",
            "South Sudan",
            "Rwanda",
            "Senegal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 47,
        question: "Khartoum is the capital of?",
        answer: "Sudan",
        options: [
            "Morocco",
            "Botswana",
            "Sudan",
            "Congo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 48,
        question: "Mbabane is the capital of?",
        answer: "Swaziland",
        options: [
            "Malawi",
            "Burundi",
            "Mongolia",
            "Swaziland"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 49,
        question: "Dodoma is the capital of?",
        answer: "Tanzania",
        options: [
            "Mauritania",
            "Eswatini",
            "Tanzania",
            "Al Maghrib"
        ]
    },
    {
        
        numb: 50,
        question: "Lome is the capital of?",
        answer: "Togo",
        options: [
            "Togo",
            "Guinea-Bissau",
            "The Gambia",
            "Libia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 51,
        question: "Tunis is the capital of?",
        answer: "Tunisia",
        options: [
            "Brunei",
            "Mali",
            "Eritrea",
            "Tunisia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 52,
        question: "Kampala is the capital of?",
        answer: "Uganda",
        options: [
            "Algeria",
            "Uganda",
            "Burundi",
            "Angola"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 53,
        question: "Lusaka is the capital of?",
        answer: "Zambia",
        options: [
            "Zambia",
            "Paraguay",
            "Eritera",
            "Burundi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 54,
        question: "Harare is the capital of?",
        answer: "Zimbabwe",
        options: [
            "The Gambia",
            "Uruguay",
            "Zimbabwe",
            "Libya"
        ]
    }
];